mathgames.com 2019-05-31

# Math Games - Privacy Policy

**We Commit To:**

  * Not sell student information
  * Not behaviorally target advertising
  * Use data for authorized education purposes only
  * Not change privacy policies without notice and choice
  * Enforce strict limits on data retention
  * Support parental access to, and correction of errors in, their children’s information
  * Provide comprehensive security standards
  * Be transparent about collection and use of data.

MathGames.com (TeachMe) feels strongly about protecting your privacy and not contributing to the endless volumes of spam on the Internet.

**TeachMe will not sell, trade, or assign any non-aggregated, personally identifiable personal information that it collects to third parties.**

If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding this privacy policy please contact us.

TeachMe, Inc owns and operates a number of applications and websites, this unified privacy policy applies to all information used and collected by TeachMe, Inc and applies to MathGames ([www.mathgames.com](http://www.mathgames.com/)).

1\. Information Collected by TeachMe

In order for you to fully participate on various TeachMe websites and applications ("Services"), you must register on TeachMe. This registration process may require you to provide your name, email, location, phone number, school and grade level information of the students you're registering, and, if payment will be required for the Services, your payment information. Users can opt to use Services without registering (“Guest Mode”) however there is a chance of data loss and limited Services functionality. TeachMe makes every attempt to be as inclusive as possible towards all of our users whatever their privacy needs might be. TeachMe utilizes cookies to track, grade and create a non-identifiable profile of all users. Without cookies many aspects of our Services will not function. Information on cookies can be found in section 10 of this Privacy Policy.

2\. How TeachMe will use the information collected from you

Mailing Address: Your mailing address may be used to send you various Service materials and payment receipts. 

Email Address: Email addresses will be used to send a confirmation email at registration, as well as information and updates on current and future Services. We will also email progress reports on students as well as hints and tips on how to utilize our Services to their maximum potential. TeachMe has a dedicated area were you can control the level of email exchanged with TeachMe, a direct link to this profile control area is including in all emails. Users are free to change email preferences at any time and as often as they like – including opting out of all emails sent from TeachMe. **TeachMe will not send you unsolicited third-party promotional emails.**

Credit Card Information: With your consent, we may use and securely save your credit card information to bill you for Services provided.

Phone Number: Your phone number may serve as an alternate way of contacting you for the same purposes as email. 

Student Name: A student's name will be used to generate their username, passwords, and customize student participation with TeachMe Services.

Relationship to Student: A parent/teacher's relationship to the student will be used for profile and tracking purposes, to personalize student reports, create assignments and lesson plans and general Service feature functionality.

Additional Uses: Registration Information may be used for demographic profiling, statistical analysis, and targeted advertising. Information collected for these purposes will be aggregated as non-identifiable statistical information.

3\. Information TeachMe collects directly from a student

TeachMe collects information indirectly from a student in the form of the interactions that users make when participating with our Services. We refer to the information resulting from such participation, which includes but is not limited to data on when a student starts and stops a lesson, the responses a student makes to questions asked, the timing of a student's answers, a student's choice of character and customizations, and the choice of lessons to play as "Data." We will use Data to measure a student's performance and to adapt Programs to personalize educational needs, analyze a student's Data, and provide the student and the associated parent/educator with progress reports about student performance in the Services. In addition, we may aggregate student Data with the Data of other students participating in the Services for marketing and other business related purposes. Aggregate information will not identify individual students or parent/student relationships.

4\. Opting-out of providing the information we request

Because the TeachMe Services are individualized and customized for each student, all the information we request from you and students are required for you and a student to participate in the Services, with the exception of certain information to be used for our marketing purposes. At any time, you may revoke your consent to allowing a student to participate in TeachMe Services or refuse to allow TeachMe to further use or collect student personal information. Any non-identifiable student Data will be retained, but we will no longer use any identifiable information regarding you or a student that you have provided. However, if you do any of the foregoing, site functionally might be limited to Guest Mode functionality and previous Data cannot be recovered.

5\. Reviewing and changing your information

You may review and modify your Registration Information at any time by accessing our website at www.teachme.com.

6\. Consent

In order to use Service, you and/or your student(s)are asked to submit certain personal information about yourselves and to authorize TeachMe to use that information in a limited number of ways. We ask you and/or the student to ensure that the Parent/Teacher has reviewed and submitted Consent as part of the registration process, which will require you to consent to our collection and use of information as described above. A sample consent form is provided to parents/teachers at the time of account registration.

7\. Password Protection

Parents and Teachers have the ability to update student password on student-linked accounts. Passwords on non-linked accounts will require user validation before they can be reset. Ensure all passwords are kept confidential and avoid password reuse between students.

8\. Protecting your information

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. TeachMe has multiple security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. Services are hosted using cloud-based services provided by Amazon. If you are viewing from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection that may differ from U.S. laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States, which does not have the same data protection laws as the European Union or other regions and by providing your personal data you consent to the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

9\. Your information and third parties

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, TeachMe will not disclose the information that it obtains from you to third parties without your express written permission, or where we believe that the law requires us to disclose the information. TeachMe will not sell, trade, or assign any non-aggregated personal information that it collects to third parties. We may aggregate the information that we collect from users of our Service to create demographic profiles and performance profiles regarding the progress of students who use Service. TeachMe may share aggregated information with marketing professionals, or potential investors. This aggregated information will be compiled and reported in the form of non-identifiable group statistics only. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, as TeachMe continues to develop its business, it might sell some or all of its assets. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. An acquiring company would be required to protect all information that TeachMe collects from users of our website and Programs in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

10\. Use of cookies

As a standard practice, TeachMe uses "cookies".

A cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from our server and stored on your computer, then sent back to our server by your browser each time you access our website. Cookies enable us to track usage of our Services. In addition, cookies are required for the operation of the Services. Please note that if you refuse cookies (by turning cookies off in your browser or by clicking "don't accept", or if you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies), our Services might not work correctly.

We use cookies to improve your experience around the site, cookies allow us to: 

  * Keep track of your progress on math skills
  * Reduce the number of times you see informational popups
  * [Stripe](https://stripe.com/us/privacy) uses cookies to store our business information for processing transactions 
  * [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/ca/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) uses cookies to store our business information for processing transactions 
  * [Google](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) uses cookies to store information on how you got to our site, and provide appropriate ads
  * [SuperAwesome](https://www.superawesome.com/awesomeads-privacy-policy) uses cookies to provide appropriate ads

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.

11\. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) is designed to protect children's privacy during use of the Internet. TeachMe has implemented practices consistent with the guidelines provided by the Federal Trade Commission to date. TeachMe will never knowingly request personally identifiable information or private content from anyone under the age of 13 without parental or educator consent. If you are a parent, legal guardian, or educator of a user under 13 you may, at any time, revoke your consent to allow a student to use the Services under your subscription, refuse to allow TeachMe to further use or collect a student's personal information, or direct TeachMe to delete all identifiable information regarding a student that you have provided. To do so, please contact our Privacy Officer at the contact information below. However, if you do any of the foregoing, site functionally might be limited to Guest Mode functionality. If you would like more information about COPPA, please go to <http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.html>.

12\. The Children's Internet Protection Act (CIPA)

The Children's Internet Protection Act (CIPA) is a law enacted December 2000 to address concerns about access to offensive content over the Internet on school and library computers. CIPA imposes certain types of requirements on any school or library that receives funding support for Internet access or internal connections from the "E-rate" program - a program that makes certain technology more affordable for eligible schools and libraries. Our Services do not provide links to external resources or chat rooms, and do not contain any offensive or inappropriate matter. As a result, any school or library that uses TeachMe Programs is fully compliant with CIPA. If you would like more information about CIPA, please go to <http://www.fcc.gov/cgb/consumerfacts/cipa.html>.

13\. The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)

The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) is a law that protects the privacy of student education records. The law applies to all schools that receive funds from the U.S. Department of Education. FERPA gives parents certain rights with respect to their children's education records. These rights transfer to the student when he or she reaches the age of 18 or attends a school beyond the high school level. TeachMe is fully compliant with FERPA.

  1. 1) Any sensitive online information is transmitted over secure channels.
  2. 2) All student data are stored in ways that are not publicly accessible.
  3. 3) Security audits are regularly performed to ensure data integrity.

TeachMe does not share student information with any third parties. If a school requests that Data should be sent to a third party, with parental consent, TeachMe would send the data to the school and never directly to the third party. If you would like more information about FERPA, please go to <http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html>.

14\. Amendments

TeachMe may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you by email regarding any material changes to our privacy and security practices. Please review all revisions to the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Services after the date TeachMe has updated such policies will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms.

Last Updated: April 1st 2014

15\. Contact Us

Mail (Snail):

Attention: Privacy Officer  
TeachMe, Inc.  
Suite 200, 15332 Antioch Street  
Los Angeles, CA 90272  
United States 

Mail (Electronic):

info@teachme.com
